<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<pages>
  <page id="" title="jQuery BBQ">
    <img src="bbq.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>jQuery BBQ</h1>
    <p>Click a nav item above or below to load some delicious AJAX content! Also,
      once the content loads, feel free to further explore our savory delights by
      clicking any inline links you might see.</p>
  </page>
  <page id="404" title="Page not found" status="400">
    <img src="bbq.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>Page not found</h1>
    <p>This is a 404 error page.</p>
  </page>
  <page id="burger" title="Delicious Burgers">
    <img src="burger.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>Delicious Burgers</h1>
    <p>It might look like more food than you can eat, but trust me, you'll finish 
    this burger. What, you say you're a vegetarian? Ok then, try the
    <a href="#!chicken">Chicken</a>!</p>
  </page>
  <page id="chicken" title="Mesquite Rub Chicken">
    <img src="chicken.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>Mesquite Rub Chicken</h1>
    <p>This spicy meal might have you begging for "cerveza" but you'll be coming back for 
    seconds! Still hungry? Why not wash that chicken down with a heaping plate of
    <a href="#!kebabs">Kebabs</a>?</p>
  </page>
  <page id="kebabs" title="Savory Shish-Kebabs">
    <img src="kebabs.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>Savory Shish-Kebabs</h1>
    <p>Who doesn't like kebabs? Nobody! That's why this meat and veggie combo is sure
    to blow your mind! Still, if you aren't in the mood for wooden sticks, why not let a
    delicious <a href="#!burger">Burger</a> whet your appetite?</p>
  </page>
  <page id="kielbasa" title="Sweet Kielbasa">
    <img src="kielbasa.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>Sweet Kielbasa</h1>
    <p>One bite of this kielbasa will have you asking for the recipe, and that's a fact.
    But save some room, because while you're here, you've got to check out our fantastic
    fall-off-the-bone <a href="#!ribs">Ribs</a>!</p>
  </page>
  <page id="ribs" title="Baby-Back Ribs">
    <img src="ribs.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>Baby-Back Ribs</h1>
    <p>What's better than a half-rack of ribs? A full rack! And if you like ribs,
    which you do, you're sure to love our perfectly seared flame-broiled
    <a href="#!steak">Steak</a>!</p>
  </page>
  <page id="steak" title="Flame-Broiled Steak">
    <img src="steak.jpg" width="400" height="300"/>
    <h1>Flame-Broiled Steak</h1>
    <p>Seasoned and cooked perfectly, this amazing steak aims to please! And if you
    have room left over, don't forget to help yourself to a plate of our sweet
    <a href="#!kielbasa">Kielbasa</a>!</p>
  </page>
</pages>